# Michael Jaeschke

11539 Huebner Rd 🏫

(210)665-6967

Jaeschke.michael@outlook.com

Experienced food & beverage associate with four years in hospitality, who specialize in attention to detail and customer service. Expert in Word, Excel, PowerPoint. Pervious background includes hospitality, culinary, and software Engineering. Seeking to further my computer science career

#### **Skills**

- JavaScript/ReactJs
- Html/Css

- Bash
- JQuery
- NodeJs

# **Experience**

SEPTEMBER 2019 - CURRENT

#### Lead Restaurant Supervisor/ UTSA Aramark, San Antonio TX

Supervised 22 employees; making sure they followed strict protocol in accordance with UTSA nutritional guidelines. Expertly operate cash register, process cash and credit transactions accurately and practice all cash-handling procedures precisely. Open and close café, count down and balance cash register assist in training new cashiers

JANURARY 2014 - SEPTEMBER 2019

### Lead Restaurant Associate/ Eilan Hotel & Spa, San Antonio, TX

Remain familiar with menu items, daily specials and featured wines. Recite daily specials, knowledge of lunch and dinner menu items and follow liquor controls. Responsible for maintaining liquor controls, taking and placing all orders promptly and correctly, serving food and beverage promptly and correctly and ensuring the guest/owner check is accurate and legible.

JULY 2013 - NOVEMBER 2014

## Subway Associate / Subway Restaurants, San Antonio, TX

Prepare food neatly, accurately and in a timely manner. Check products in sandwich unit area and restock items to ensure a sufficient supply throughout the shift. Clean as instructed. Account for cash flow and inventory during the shift. Understand and adhere to all quality standards, formulas and procedures.

#### **Education**

August 2016 - Spring 2019

## **Associates of Applied Science in Computer Science / Northwest**

Vista College

August 2016 - Spring 2019

# **Associates of Arts / Northwest Vista College**

AUGUST 2010 - JUNE 2013

High School Diploma / Brandeis High School